(Howard:)I mean, for free.
(Raj:)And plus you got a rapid prototyper.
That's an expensive piece of equipment.
(Leonard:)The rest of us have had our budgets
cut to the bone.
(Howard:)Okay, one way to look at this is that
I'm getting new equipment and you're not...
(Howard:)...and that's unfair.
(Howard:)But a better way to look at this
is that I'm getting sex and you're not.
(Howard:)And that's delightful.
(Penny:)The whole thing froze.
I don't know what happened.
(Leonard:)Calm down. We'll figure it out.
(Penny:)How can I calm down?
I'm gonna lose my shopping cart.
(Penny:)That's three hours of picking out shoes
just shot to hell.
- Hello, Penny.
- Hello, Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)You're in my spot.
- Are you planning on sitting here?
- No, I'm going to the comic-book store.
(Penny:)- What difference does it make?
- What difference?
(Leonard:)Here we go.
(Sheldon:)That is my spot.
(Sheldon:)In an ever-changing world,
it is a single point of consistency.
(Sheldon:)If my life were expressed as a function...
(Sheldon:)...on a four-dimensional
Cartesian coordinate system...